So, do you just have reeking breath that you're trying to get rid of?
Well, my name's Michelle, and I'm a dental assistant with Solutionz, and I'm here to explain to you what you can do to get better breath.
Of course, you're going to want to brush and floss your teeth three times a day, and also, you can purchase like an over-the-counter mouth rinse with rinsing with this at least twice a day will help with kind of maintaining that nice fresh breath.
You also too, it's pretty easy on on how to use.
You just want to read the directions on the back, pour the solution into the cap, and then just swish around with it.
You can sometimes what happens too, if you tend to feel that you cannot swish around with the time that it's recommending; you can dilute the mouth rinse.
This is not going to cause any difference in in the solution.
It's just going to cause' due to the alcohol content that is in it that's why you're getting that burning sensation, so if you just pour fifty percent of water and fifty percent of the mouth rinse into the cap and then just swish around this will kinda' help; therefore, where you're able to rinse with it for the good one to two minutes of the recommended time.
If you can rinse with it a little bit longer than that that'll be great because you can, it's just going to help you maintain that fresh breath.
Also too, if you don't have access to a mouth rinse, what you can do; a natural way to kind of maintain a a fresh breath is chewing on cloves, which you can easily purchase at the food store.
You just pop a clove in your mouth and kind of suck on it and chew on it for about one to two minutes.
This will kind of create a nice fresh type of clove scent in your mouth.
These are all great ways on how to get fresher breath, but you definitely need to see your general dentist if you notice that you are doing these things and you're not taking care of the problem, and you still just have that stinky breath.
You definitely want to check out with your doctor or your dentist to see what you can do that will help you with that in the long run.
Once again, my name is Michelle, and I'm a dental assistant with Solutionz, and I just explained to you on how you can maintain your fresh breath.